A Guide to the China Medical Board, Inc. records, RG 1 FA065
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Liu, Shao-kwang, 1924-1931 (Box 83, Folder 589A)
- Liu, S. P. - Loeber (Box 83, Folder 590)
  Liu, Shih-pao, 1924-1928; Liu, Wen-han, 1959, 1965; Liu, Yung-yao, 1939-1946; Loan Funds, 1926-1940 (Cochrane, Thomas; Comptroller; Director; Greene; Sun Ching-fen Memorial; Svea A. Lindberg Memorial); Lobenstine, E. C., 1937; Lockhart Hall, 1927 (Director); Loeber, Isabel (Mrs.), 1920.
  Items of special note in this folder include a Report on the Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) (1937), found under the mark-up Lobenstine.
- London Missionary Society (B-G) (Box 84, Folder 591)
  Brown, T. Crocker, 1937; Cochrane, Thomas, 1915-1929, 1934-1935, 1944, 1954; Gregg, 1946-1947
- London Missionary Society - Hawkins, F. H., 1915-1936 (Box 84, Folder 592)
- Lon-Lum (Box 84, Folder 593)
  London School of Hygiene, 1930 (Greene); Lu, 1926; Lu, George, 1929; Lu, Go, 1947; Lu, Hung-tien, 1926-1927; Lu, Jen-lung, 1954; Lu, (Yueh-han) John, 1947-1948; Lu, Sung-nien, 1952-1954; Lu, (Yung-o) Virginia, 1946-1947; Lu, Wan-ching, 1946-1947; Lu, Wei-shan, 1945-1950; Lu, Yi-chuang, 1954; Lum, Bertha, 1945
- Ma, D. - Ma, R. M. (Box 84, Folder 594)
  Ma, (Yueh-ching) Dorothy, 1938-1941, 1947-1956, 1962-1966; Ma, (Yung-chiang) Joseph, 1945-1947; Ma, Kiam, 1923-1926, 1959; Ma, Roberta M., 1927.
  Items of special note in this folder include a photograph of (Yueh-ching) Dorothy Ma's daughter and house (February 8, 1966).
- Macmillan, Eva B. A., 1919-1922 (Box 84, Folder 595)
- Macmillan, Eva B. A., 1923-1925 (Box 84, Folder 596)
- Macmillan, Eva B. A., 1926-1927 (Box 84, Folder 597)
- Macmillan, Eva B. A., 1928-1941 (Box 84, Folder 598)
- Macmillan, Eva B. A., 1942-1971 (Box 85, Folder 599)
- Mad-Max (Box 85, Folder 600)
  Madsen, Th. J. M., 1927, 1930; Mail, 1921, 1930-1932, 1936-1940, 1947-1950 (Comptroller; Director; Greene; Hogg; Houghton; Loucks; Memo); Mallett, John, 1933-1934; Man and Medicine, 1932-1933 (Greene; Sigerist); Manshardt, Clifford, 1939; Mao, H. C., 1924-1925; Marshall, W. A., 1918; Marr, Norman J., 1925-1926; Mass Education Movement, 1932-1936, 1939, 1944-1945, 1953, 1960-1961, 1965 (Chen, Chih-chien; Grant, J. B.; Greene, R. S;. Houghton; Yen, Y. C. James); Mathewson, C. H., 1918; Maxwell-Woo Fund, 1939
- McC-McK (Box 85, Folder 601)
  McCartney, J. L., 1923-1927; McCormick Athletic Fund, 1932; McCoy, M. Louise, 1919-1924, 1935, 1962, 1964, 1968; McCoy, Mary, 1935; McDonald, Jessie, 1927; McGill, Charles S., 1925-1926; McGill University - Penfield, Wilder, 1929, 1936-1939, 1944, 1962-1967; McKhann, Charles F., 1927, 1930-1942
- McL-Med (Box 85, Folder 602)
  McLean, Franklin C., 1920, 1924 (see also Director, and Union Medical College); Meade, Richard H., 1943, 1954; Media Resources Corporation, 1971; Medical College of Virginia, 1947-1950 (Evans, Everett I.); Medical Education in China, 1942; Medical Education for Women, 1916, 1919, 1921 (Beebe, R. C.; Greene; Hodge, Margaret E.; Houghton; Miner, Luella); Medical Faculty - Minutes, 1920-1937; Medical Missionary Association, 1915-1926, 1935 (Anderson, Webb; Churchill, H. Melville; Maxwell, James L.; Wenham, Arthur); Medical School of National Nanking University, 1949; Medical School Survey, 1923; Medical Textbooks, 1933-1935 (Comptroller; Greene; Houghton).
  Items of special note in this folder include a memo re: Obligation of Trustees to Staff of Peking Union Medical College (1920), found under the mark-up McLean.
- Medicine, 1916-1925 (Box 85, Folder 603)
- Medicine, 1926-1927 (Box 85, Folder 604)
- Medicine, 1928-1941 (Box 85, Folder 605)
  Director; Flexner; Greene; Houghton; Peabody, F. W.; Pearce, R. M.; Resident Director; Robertson, O. H.
  Items of special note in this file include a plot plan of the Medicine Department.
- Medicine - Interne, 1921-1932 (Box 86, Folder 606)
- Medicine - Interne, 1933-1941 (Box 86, Folder 607)
  American Baptist Foreign Mission Society - Lerrigo, P. H. Jr.; American Board of Commissioners for Foreign Missions - Strong, Wm. E.; Baptist Mission Society - Fullerton, W. Y.; Barnes, Richard; Chan, Yik-ping; Chang, S. K. P.; China Inland Mission - Martin, John B.; Church Missionary Society - Bardsley, C.; Church of the Brethren - Bonsack, Charles D.; Director; Form Letters; Greene; Houghton; Hsiung, Ju-cheng; King, James D.; Liu, J. Heng; Macallum, A. B.; Macmillan, E. A. B.; Martin, C. F.; McLean, Franklin C.; Methodist Church (Canada;) Methodist Episcopal Church; North, Frank M.; Obias, Mirardo; Peabody; Presbyterian Church (Brown, Arthur J.; Chester, S. H.); Presbyterian Church of England; Protestant Episcopal Church - Wood, John W.; Reformed Church in America - Chamberlain, William I.; Sloan, T. Dwight; Society for the Propagation of the Gospel; Student Volunteer Movement for Foreign Missions; Svenska Missionsforbundet - Lundall, Jakol E.; Tilaka; United Christian Missioner Society - Corey, Stephen J.; United Evangelical Lutheran Church in America; United Free Church of Scotland - Ashcroft, Frank P.; Wells; Wesleyan Methodist Mission Society - Wigfield, Frederick P.; Woman's Union Mission Society of America
- Medicine - Staff (A) (Box 86, Folder 608)
  Alloway, J. Lionel, 1925-1942, 1947, 1950; Amoss, Harold L., 1926, 1931-1933, 1956; Au-Young, Chung-wo, 1934-1936
- Medicine - Staff (Ba-Be) (Box 86, Folder 609)
  Barrera, Alberto M., 1941, 1946; Bau, (Ching-ming) Benjamin, 1925-1927; Beh, Yin-tsai, 1935; Berglund, Hilding, 1923, 1927-1931, 1962
- Medicine - Staff - Bien, (Wan-nien) Charles, 1930-1941, 1945-1954, 1964 (Box 86, Folder 610)
- Medicine - Staff (Bo-Bu) (Box 86, Folder 611)
  Boots, (Ralph H.), 1923; Bowin, Lucy E., 1923; Brown, Cabot, 1924-1927; Brown, N. Worth, 1916-1919; Bume, G. F., 1923
- Medicine - Staff (Chan - Chang, M. H.) (Box 86, Folder 612)
  Chan, Yik-ping, 1924-1926; Chang, An, 1948-1949; Chang, Ching-jung, 1940; Chang, Hsiao-chien, 1924-1936, 1942-1950, 1966; Chang, Hsioh-teh, 1941, 1948-1950; Chang, Hung, 1949-1950; Chang, Ming-hung, 1931
- Medicine - Staff - Chang, Stephen (Kuang-pi), 1933-1945 (Box 86, Folder 613)
  See also folder 618 - Medicine - Staff - Chen, K. C., 5/9/1971, and folder 1138 - United States - State Department - Kelley, 1/29/1944
- Medicine - Staff - Chang, Stephen (Kuang-pi), 1946 (Box 87, Folder 614)
- Medicine - Staff - Chang, Stephen (Kuang-pi), 1947 (Box 87, Folder 615)
- Medicine - Staff - Chang, Stephen (Kuang-pi), 1948-1968 (Box 87, Folder 616)
- Medicine - Staff (Chang, T. S. 0 Cheer) (Box 87, Folder 617)
  Chang, Tsge-shun, 1930; Chang, Wei-hsui, 1929; Chang, Wen-san, 1930, 1947; Chang, Yao-hsien, 1937; Chang, Yu-hui, 1950; Chao, Chen-ming, 1924; Chao, Chih-pu, 1939-1940; Chao, Hsi-ang, 1925; Chao, Min-hsueh, 1935-1936; Chao, Shu-lien, 1933; Cheer, Sheo-nan, 1923-1933, 1951, 1957, 1964-1967
- Medicine - Staff (Chen, D. S. - Chiang, R.) (Box 87, Folder 618)
  Chen, Dao-sen, 1925; Chen, Grace, 1936; Chen, Hsi-li, 1931-1933; Chen, Hsi-sheng, 1939; Chen, Hsi-tao, 1950; Chen, Jui-tzu, 1930; Chen, Kung-li, 1925; Chen, Kuo-chen, 1933-1940, 1971 (see also Publications - Chinese Medical Journal); Chen, Kwoh-kuang, 1940; Chen, Mei-hua, 1934; Chen, Philip, 1930; Chen, (Chung-yao) Samuel, 1938; Chen, Shu-hsum, 1950; Chen, Shun-ming, 1926-1927; Chen, S. P., 1922; Chen, Teh, 1929; Chen, Tsung-shun, 1934; Chen, Wu-ming, 1938; Chen, Yin-ho, 1934-1935; Cheng, Chao-ling (Ernest), 1930; Cheng, Chien-shih, 1929; Chi, Chen-yuan, 1929; Chi, Ching-hsin, 1927; Chi, Ming, 1950; Chi, S. C., 1927; Chia, Kuei, 1926; Chiang, Chao-chu, 1931; Chiang, Chin-hua, 1934; Chiang, Mo-ching, 1935; Chiang, (Yu-Ying), Richard, 1926
- Medicine - Staff (Chiang, Y. T. - Chu, Y.) (Box 87, Folder 619)
  Chiang, Yu-tu, 1939, 1940, 1947-1949; Chien, I. C./Chu; Chien, I-chien, 1940; Chien, Mu-han, 1924-1925; Chien, Yu-bing, 1949; Chin, Chen-ting, 1937; Chin, Shih-hsin, 1940; Chou, Shou-kai, 1933-1934, 1947; Chow, (Mu-ying) Anna, 1930; Chow, Chien, 1924; Chu, Cheng-fang, 1933, 1937; Chu, Fu-fang, 1928-1929; Chu, Hsien-i, 1933, 1936-1938, 1942-1949 (see also Publications - Chinese Medical Journal); Chu, Shih-ying, 1927; Chu, Yien, 1934
- Medicine - Staff (Chung - Connell) (Box 87, Folder 620)
  Chung, Huei-lan (William), 1930-1941, 1945-1950, 1958 (see also Publications - Chinese Medical Journal); Colberg, Arthur J., 1921-1923, 1960; Connell, John W., 1923-1924
- Medicine - Staff - Dieuaide, Francis R., 1923-1929 (Box 87, Folder 621)
  Dieuaide, Ruth G. (Mrs.)
- Medicine - Staff - Dieuaide, Francis R., 1930-1942, 1945-1951, 1964 (Box 88, Folder 622)
- Medicine - Staff (Dj-Du) (Box 88, Folder 623)
  Djung, Ida G., 1939; Dschen, Tsun-chi, 1940-1941; Du, Swun-deh, 1926
- Medicine - Staff (E) (Box 88, Folder 624)
  Edsall, David L., 1924-1936 (see also Howard University); Erskine, Earle B., 1935
- Medicine - Staff (Fa-Fi) (Box 88, Folder 625)
  Fan, Chuan, 1930; Fan, Hai-shan, 1932-1933; Fan, Yueh-cheng, 1934-1935; Fang, Chun-pin, 1948; Fang, I-chi, 1926-1927; Fang, Kan, 1933; Fang, Yung-lu, 1941; Feng, Schwee-lien, 1940; Feng, Yen-chen, 1935; Feng, Ying-kun, 1934-1937, 1949; Feng, Yu-shan, 1935-1937; Fernando, Felino, 1925-1927, 1940; Firor, Marion P., 1924-1927; Fitzmaurice, Lawrence W., 1925-1926, 1941, 1952
- Medicine - Staff (Fo-Fu) (Box 88, Folder 626)
  Forkner, Claude E., 1930-1943, 1964; Fox, Ruth, 1925-1927, 1931-1933, 1936; Fu, Shou-shan, 1948
- Medicine - Staff (G) (Box 88, Folder 627)
  Gault, Arabella S., 1922-1926; Grant, J. B., 1925; Guy, Ruth, 1923-1929, 1937, 1945-1946, 1971 (see also above Dieuaide)
- Medicine - Staff (Ha-Han) (Box 88, Folder 628)
  Ha, Han-wan, 1934; Hahn, Young D., 1925-1926; Hall, Giles A. M., 1932-1937; Hannon, Roger R., 1926, 1930-1936, 1960, 1964.
  Items of special note in this folder include a photograph of Roger R. Hannon (September 26, 1930), found under the mark-up Medicine - Staff - Hannon.
- Medicine - Staff (Har-Ho) (Box 88, Folder 629)
  Hardy, Albert V., 1923-1930; Harrop, George A., 1923-1924; Hayne, J. Hester, 1933-1936, 1942; Ho, (Pi-hui), Frances, 1931; Ho, Fu-chuan, 1924; Ho, Howell, 1931; Ho, Sheng-lu, 1927
- Medicine - Staff (Hou - Hu) (Box 89, Folder 630)
  Hou, Hsiang-chuan, 1924; Hou, Yu-hwa, 1950; Houghton, Henry S., 1924; Hsiang, Chuan-shen, 1924; Hsieh, Hsi-hsu, 1931; Hsieh, (Wen-lien) Lily S., 1931, 1954; Hsu, Chi-ho, 1932-1933; Hsu, Chi-liang, 1926-1927; Hsu, Chien-liang, 1931; Hsu, Han-kuang, (Katherine), 1938-1941, 1959-1960; Hsu, Huan-yun, 1950; Hsu, Hwei-chuan, 1938-1940; Hsu, Lien-po, 1940; Hsu, S. L., 1925; Hsu, Shih-shun, 1931, 1952; Hsu, Su-en, 1931-1933; Hsu, Tien-yi, 1934-1935, 1944; Hsu, Ying-kuei, 1932-1933; Hsu, Yu-hui, 1937; Hsueh, Chying-yu, 1939; Hsueh, Pang-chi, 1937; Hsueh, Pei-chi, 1926; Hu, Chuan-kuei, 1926-1927; Hu, Rose, 1950; Hu, Ying-teh, 1924-1925.
  Items of special note in this folder include a photograph of Han-kuang (Katherine) Hsu and Dora Chao (July 25, 1959), found under the mark-up Medicine - Staff - Hsu, Han-kuang (Katherine).
- Medicine - Staff (Hua-Hun) (Box 89, Folder 631)
  Huang, Chen-hsiang, 1934-1935, 1941-1947; Huang, Huei-hsui, 1931; Huang, Jen-jo, 1933-1934, 1953; Huang, Ke-kang, 1930; Huang, Keh-wei, 1933-1934, 1946-1947; Huang, S. Grace, 1935; Huang, Shu-yun, 1935-1936; Huang, Tsui-mei, 1934-1937; Huang, Wen-yu, 1924; Hung, Ta-shen, 1950
- Medicine - Staff (Jo-Ki) (Box 89, Folder 632)
  Johnson, Hosmer F., 1926-1927, 1952-1957; Johnston, Kenneth B., 1922-1924; Jung, Tu-shan, 1928; Kang, Shih-ying, 1934; Kao, Wei, 1924-1926; Ke, Ju-ting, 1931; Keefer, Chester S., 1928-1932, 1964; Kellers, Irmarita, 1921-1924; King, James D., 1934-1935, 1949; King, Li-pin, 1924, 1942
- Medicine - Staff - Korns, John H., 1917-1928, 1933, 1940, 1962, 1965 (Box 89, Folder 633)
  Korns, Mary
- Medicine - Staff (Ku-Kw) (Box 89, Folder 634)
  Kumm, Henry W., 1925-1927, 1964-1965; Kuttner, Ann G., 1933, 1936; Kuo, Mei-sun, 1933; Kuo, Te-lung, 1936-1937; Kwei, Hsiung-wu (Samuel), 1925-1928; Kwoh, Fang-ying, 1936-1937
- Medicine - Staff (Lan-Lee) (Box 89, Folder 635)
  Lang, Chien-wei, 1925, 1934-1935; Law, Fon-mong, 1937-1938; Lee, Chung-un, 1923-1938, 1947-1949, 1953, 1957, 1963; Lee, (Y. C.) George, 1932-1939; Lee, Hah-liong, 1934; Lee, Jui-ling, 1928; Lee, (Chung-hau) Robert, 1934-1938
- Medicine - Staff (Lee-Lei) (Box 89, Folder 636)
  Lee, Violet, 1939 (Li, Hsiu-ching); Lee, Yong-kyum, 1934-1935; Lei, Ai-te, 1938; Lei, Tsoi-laan, 1933; Leitch, Gordon B., 1925-1927.
  Items of special note in this folder include a photograph of Gordon B. Leitch (December 8, 1925), found under the mark-up Medicine - Staff - Leitch.
- Medicine - Staff - Lennox, William G., 1915-1925, 1960 (Box 89, Folder 637)
- Medicine - Staff (Li - Ling) (Box 90, Folder 638)
  Li, Benjamin, 1935; Li, Chia-yi, 1949; Li, Ching-chieh, 1936, 1945; Li, En-sheng, 1948-1950; Li, Gi-ming, 1938-1940; Li, Hsi-kun, 1940-1941; Li, Hsui-chun, 1929; Li, Hui-fang, 1940; Li, Pang-chi, 1948-1950; Li, Pei-gwang, 1929; Li, Pi-hsia, 1934-1936; Li, (Chu) R. C., 1930; Li, Shao-hua, 1938; Li, Shih-we, 1925-1927; Li, Tien-chueh, 1924; Li, Wen-re, 1929; Li, Wen-jen, 1941; Li, Wen-ming (William), 1930; Liang, Chi-hsuan, 1936; Liang, Ping-yee, 1934-1935, 1940, 1945, 1953; Liang, Yih-chang, 1949; Liao, Puh-ying, 1936; Lien, Chih-hao, 1950; Lieu, Kuk-waung, 1927; Lieu, Vi-tuh, 1933, 1945-1947, 1954 (see also Publications - Chinese Medical Journal); Lim, Kean-hock, 1948; Lin, Chiao-chih, 1928; Lin, Ching-kwei, 1930; Lin, Chuan-hsiang, 1948; Lin, Fei-ching, 1931; Lin, Feng-san, 1925; Lin, Hazel; 1934-1935; Lin, Kien-pong, 1939-1940; Lin, Sung, 1932; Ling, Chi, 1948; Ling, Chih-huan, 1939, 1964, 1969; Ling, Chih-ming, 1940; Ling, Hsiao-ying (Jeannette), 1927; Ling, Yung-tung, 1938-1940
- Medicine - Staff (Liu) (Box 90, Folder 639)
  Liu, Ching-pan, 1926-1927; Liu, Chong-en, 1927; Liu, Hsi-lin, 1924-1925; Liu, Hsu-chen, 1950; Liu, Hwa-yang, 1924; Liu, King-ban, 1926-1927; Liu, Kuo-cheng, 1950; Liu, Pao-young, 1925-1928; Liu, Shao-wu, 1940-1941; Liu, Shih-hao, 1924-1941, 1945-1951 (see also Publications - Chinese Medical Journal); Liu, Shu-wan, 1924-1926, 1942-1944; Liu, Trevor C., 1937; Liu, Wei-chi, 1948; Liu, Wei-ching, 1948; Liu, Wei-tung, 1937-1946 (see also Publications - Chinese Medical Journal); Liu, William L., 1929; Liu, Y-tsou, 1940; Liu, Yao-kwen, 1930
- Medicine - Staff (Lo - Luo) (Box 90, Folder 640)
  Lo, Ren-chieh, 1935; Loh, Ven-tsao, 1921-1922, 1929, 1934; Louie, Stanley, 1936-1937, 1942; Lu, Chung-shen, 1937; Lu, (Y. C.) George, 1924-1929, 1945; Lu, Hung-tien, 1930, 1971; Lu, Jui-ping, 1934-1936, 1941; Lu, Kuan-chuan, 1936; Lu, Su-hsien, 1931; Luo, Tsung-hsien, 1931.
  Items of special note in this folder include a photograph of Stanley Louie (December 21, 1936), found under the mark-up Medicine - Staff - Louie.
- Medicine - Staff (Ma-Mel) (Box 90, Folder 641)
  Ma, Chia-chi (Thomas), 1933-1934, 1944-1946, 1968 (includes Esther Tye); Ma, Chung-teh, 1934-1935; Ma, Hsi-ting, 1927; Ma, Ling-feng, 1948; Ma, Wan-sen, 1933-1938 (see also Publications - Chinese Medical Journal); Ma, Yueh-ching, 1933; Maguire, Clarence E., 1925-1927, 1935, 1942; Mao, Yen-wu, 1936; Marlow, Arthur A., 1932-1956; Marriott, 1925; McGill, Charles S., 1923-1924; McIntosh, John F., 1928-1933, 1964-1966.
  Items of special note in this folder include a photograph of Clarence E. Maguire (December 21, 1925), found under the mark-up Medicine - Staff - Maguire; and a photograph of Arthur A. Marlow (August 13, 1932), found under the mark-up Medicine - Staff - Marlow.
- Medicine - Staff - McLean, Franklin C., 1916-1934, 1950, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 642)
  Items of special note in this folder include a Docket - Executive Committee of Trustees of the Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) (December 13, 1917) and a list of persons attending Trustee Dinner (June 6, 1918).
- Medicine - Staff (Mei - Mi) (Box 90, Folder 643)
  Mei, Cheuk-shang, 1921; Mei, Y. C., 1933; Meleney, Henry E., 1922-1927, 1958, 1963-1971; Mi, Ching-hsien, 1933-1935
- Medicine - Staff (Mi-Pi) (Box 90, Folder 644)
  Miao, Hsiu-zen, 1935-1936; Mills, Clarence A., 1926-1929; Mills, R. G., 1924; Ni, Yin-yuan, 1923, 1926, 1932; Nieh, Chung-en, 1934-1935; Obias, Mirardo P., 1923-1924; Ouyang, (Hsu-ming) George, 1935-1937; Pan, Ming-tzu, 1924-1925; Pan, Tso-hsu, 1930; Pan, Wai-lo, 1925; Pan, Wei-tu, 1925, 1931; Pang, Samuel H. (see below Phang); Pao, Kwang-yih, 1950; Peabody, Francis W., 1922-1928; Phang, Samuel H., 1933-1936, 1940-1941, 1945; Pian, Hsueh-chien, 1936-1938; Piggott, Richard, 1924.
  Items of special note in this folder include a photograph of Samuel H. Phang (September 17, 1933), found under the mark-up Medicine - Staff - Phang.
- Medicine - Staff (Ra-Rh) (Box 91, Folder 645)
  Ramey, W. Orville, 1925-1926; Rappleye, W. C., 1924; Reimann, Hobart A., 1927-1934, 1962-1967; Rhee, Soo-won, 1925
- Medicine - Staff - Robertson, Oswald H., 1916-1927, 1946, 1960, 1966 (Box 91, Folder 646)
- Medicine - Staff (Rob-Roc) (Box 91, Folder 647)
  Robinson, G. Canby, 1934-1935, 1951; Rockwell, Alice E., 1921-1923, 1966
- Medicine - Staff (Sa-Si) (Box 91, Folder 648)
  Sang, Pei-en (Paul), 1925; Sha, Jung-hui, 1950; Shang, Wen-yi, 1936-1937; Shao, Hsiao-hung, 1950; Shen, Chen-kun, 1936; Shen, (Chi-ying) Dorothy, 1923-1933; Shen, Tien-chueh, 1940; Shen, Yu-chuan, 1933; Shepherd, Pearl, 1923-1924; Shih, Ching-jen, 1926-1927; Shih, Hsi-en, 1928; Shih, Hsueh-chun, 1938; Shih, Hsueh-hui, 1925-1927; Shiong, Bi-swang, 1935; Sia, (Ho-ping) Richard, 1919-1939, 1945, 1970; Siao, Chi-hoah, 1938
- Medicine - Staff - Smyly, H. Jocelyn, 1916-1931, 1957, 1960, 1964-1965 (Box 91, Folder 649)
- Medicine - Staff - Snapper, Isadore, 1927-1940 (Box 91, Folder 650)
  Items of special note in this folder include a Baccalaureate Address (June 4, 1937).
- Medicine - Staff - Snapper, Isadore, 1941 (Box 91, Folder 651)
- Medicine - Staff - Snapper, Isadore, 1942-1965 (Box 91, Folder 652)
- Medicine - Staff (So-Sz) (Box 92, Folder 653)
  Soong, Yuin-dzing, 1930; Stainsby, Wendell J., 1925-1928, 1938; Stucki, John C., 1923-1926; Su, Chi-chen, 1935-1936 (see also Publications - Chinese Medical Journal); Su, Tsu-fei, 1931-1937, 1946-1948; Sun, Franklin M., 1938; Sun, Hui-min, 1937-1941; Sun, Wen-tsang, 1949-1950; Sun, Yun-chan, 1925; Sung, Chieh, 1933-1936; Sung, Chih-wang, 1925-1926; Sung, Lu, 1941; Sze, Tseng-sing, 1932-1933
- Medicine - Staff (Tai - Tien) (Box 92, Folder 654)
  Tai, Lien-kiang, 1934; Tai, Tze-ying, 1937-1938; Tait, Ruth, 1925; Tan, Chung-chang, 1938; Tang, Chwen-seng, 1938-1940; Tang, Han-chih, 1926-1927, 1949, 1954-1956, 1965; Tang, Tze-kuang, 1928, 1947; Tang, Yung-sung, 1935; Teng, Chia-tung, 1933-1942, 1948-1950, 1963; Teng, Chin-hsien, 1937-1938, 1945, 1950; Teng, Ching-tseng, 1941, 1946, 1949-1957, 1962-1964; Tien, Yu-tao, 1939-1940
- Medicine - Staff (Til-Tun) (Box 92, Folder 655)
  Tilaka, Yai (Lucy), 1923-1927, 1966; Ting, Tsan, 1941-1946; Ting, Yung-hoo, 1923; Toong, Dau-tsu, 1938-1940; Trask, James D., 1927; Tsao, 1939; Tsen, Shih-ping, 1925; Tseng, (H. W.) Clinton, 1922-1923; Tung, Chen-lang, 1923-1945 (see also Publications - Chinese Medical Journal); Tung, Tien-hua, 1949; Tung, Tsun, 1933; Tung, Yu-heng, 1940
- Medicine - Staff (Van Sant - Wang, J. T.) (Box 92, Folder 656)
  Van Sant, Helen V., 1923-1929, 1946, 1956, 1965, 1969; Wan, Fu-en (Franklin), 1925-1926, 1931, 1940; Wang, An-taim, 1940; Wang, Basil, 1935, 1945-1947; Wang, Cheng-I, 1938, 1943-1946; Wang, Chi-wu, 1933-1944 (see also Publications - Chinese Medical Journal); Wang, Chia-cheng, 1926; Wang, Chia-hsiang, 1930; Wang, Chung-fang, 1938-1941; Wang, Hsi, 1925; Wang, Hsin-fen, 1937; Wang, Hui-ling, 1949-1950; Wang, Hung-wen, 1935-1937; Wang, Jun-tien, 1938-1940, 1944, 1959, 1963.
  Items of special note in this folder include a photograph of a Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) diploma (1944), found under the mark-up Medicine - Staff - Wang, Cheng-I.
- Medicine - Staff (Wang, K. C. - Wight) (Box 92, Folder 657)
  Wang, Kuang-chao, 1940; Wang, Kuo-cheng, 1928, 1935-1937, 1941, 1945; Wang, Ling-sun, 1933; Wang, Pei-wo, 1931; Wang, Shao-hsun, 1933; Wang, Shih-leng, 1949; Wang, Shih-tsuan, 1940; Wang, Shih-wei, 1927; Wang, Shu-hsieti, 1929, 1936-1940, 1946; Wang, Tchin-I, 1950; Want, Te-yen, 1941; Wang, Wei-hua, 1940; Wang, Wen-yuan, 1931; Wang, Y. K., 1919-1920; Wight, George E., 1924-1926
- Medicine - Staff - Willner, Otto, 1921-1926 (Box 92, Folder 658)
- Medicine - Staff - Willner, Otto, 1927-1928 (Box 92, Folder 659)
- Medicine - Staff - Willner, Otto, 1929-1963 (Box 93, Folder 660)
- Medicine - Staff (Wo-Wy) (Box 93, Folder 661)
  Wong, Chen-hua, 1948; Wong, Fun-chee, 1950; Wong, Hung-hsun, 1931; Woo, Cushing, 1930; Woo, G. G., 1924; Woo, Ming-shu, 1925; Woo, Shu-tai, 1922-1931; Wu, Chao-jen, 1927-1935; Wu, Chi-wen, 1933; Wu, Chih-chung, 1932-1936, 1948; Wu, Chung-ya, 1949; Wu, Fah-yu, 1925; Wu, Fang-chen, 1933, 1937; Wu, Hung-tek, 1935-1936; Wu, Kung-liang, 1934-1935; Wu, Jui-ping, 1939; Wu, William Quo, 1938-1939, 1947; Wylie, John H., 1925-1926, 1929
- Medicine - Staff (Yang - Yoh) (Box 93, Folder 662)
  Yang, Chi-shih, 1925-1931, 1942-1945, 1963; Yang, Chien-pang, 1933; Yang, Ining-shih, 1931; Yang, Kyueh-tsung, 1934; Yang, (Pao-chun) Lth, 1925-1928; Yang, Wen-tah, 1935-1936; Yang, Yueh-ying, 1935-1936, 1956-1957; Yao, Erh-chang, 1922; Yao, Hsun-yuan, 1925-1931, 1942; Yao, Kefang, 1925; Yeh, Kung-shao, 1934-1935, 1941-1942; Yen, Chen-hui, 1931; Yen, Chien-tien, 1922; Yen, Hui-ching, 1923-1935, 1947, 1950; Yen, Jen-ying, 1940; Yoh, Tse-fei, 1940-1941
- Medicine - Staff - Young, Charles W., 1914-1927 (Box 93, Folder 663)
- Medicine - Staff - Young, Charles W., 1928-1929 (Box 93, Folder 664)
- Medicine - Staff (Box 93, Folder 665)
  Young, Edward S., 1935-1937; Young, Olivia (Mrs. Charles W.), 1929-1942, 1958
- Medicine - Staff (Yu - Yung) (Box 93, Folder 666)
  Yu, (A. F.) Evelyn, 1948; Yu, Huan-wen, 1934; Yu, Sung-ting, 1938; Yu, Tsai-fan, 1935-1938, 1955 (see also Publications - Chinese Medical Journal); Yuan, I-Chin, 1926-1927, 1936, 1947; Yuan, Yih-kwang, 1931-1932; Yui, (Hsien-en) John, 1934-1935; Yung, Winston W., 1931
- Mee-Mel (Box 93, Folder 667)
  Meetings, 1939, 1945-1948; Mei, Lan-fang, 1929-1930; Mei, Y. L., 1926, 1943-1944; Meleney, Henry, 1947-1948, 1953
- Met-Mic (Box 94, Folder 668)
  Methodist Mission Hospital - Ling-ling, Hunan, 1943; "Methods and Problems of Medical Education," 1933 (Greene); Metropolitan Hospital, 1932 (Fang, Shi-san; Greene); Metropolitan Library, 1928 (Greene); Metropolitan Insurance Co, 1947-1948 (Comptroller; Director; Loucks); Michael Reese Hospital - Cutler, M. (see Surgery Staff); Microfilms, 1943-1945 (Army Medical Library [Brinkley, C.]; Forkner; United States State Department [Dennis, W. H.; Fairbanks, W. C.; Hanson, H.])
- Mid-Min (Box 94, Folder 669)
  Midwifery, 1926-1932, 1937-1938 (Director; Gee; Grant, J. B.; Greene; Gregg; Ingram, Ruth; Maxwell; Resident Director); Millbank Memorial Fund, 1931-1932 (Grant, Greene); Millbank, Tweed, Hadley & McCoy, 1944-1950, 1967 (Charter and By-laws; Hamilton, Sinclair; Parkinson; Trustees - Thomas); Miles, L. J. (Mrs.), 1924-1925; Miller, C. Phillips, 1929-1930; Miller, Gavin G., 1922-1924, 1948, 1961, 1964; Mills, Frances V., 1967, 1971; Miner, Luella, 1919; Ministry of Education, 1929; Ministry of Health, 1948
- Minutes - Correspondence, 1928-1934 (Box 94, Folder 670)
  Chien, Archibald P.; Debevoise, T. M.; Director; Fosdick; Greene
- Minutes - Correspondence, 1934-1949 (Box 94, Folder 671)
- Mis-Mod (Box 94, Folder 672)
  Missionary Research Library, 1957; Mo, (S. P.) Paul, 1928, 1932; "Modern Hospital," 1923 (Weber); Modern Languages, 1917-1926 (Director; Houghton; Macmillan, E. B. A.; Pearce, R. M.; Resident Director; Stifler, W. W.; Uspensky (see U); Wilson, Kenneth); Modern Languages - Chinese (Chen, Yung, 1926-1928; Fang, Shisan-chin, 1928-1929; Greene, 1928-1930; Kiang, Vung-shi, 1929, 1933-1941, 1945)